<resources>

    <string name="app_name">GoForward</string>
    <string name="main_title">News feed</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="Feeds">

        [

            \"revenue\":{
            \"image\":\"@drawable/revenue\",
            \"date\":\"July 27 at 21:25\",
            \"text\":\"Today government collects Shs 12,000 billion per annum which has enabled us to provide essential facilities and services. More schools, roads, electricity, health centers have been provided because the Government has got good revenue.\",
            \"likes\":\"1.5K Likes\",
            \"Comments\":\"800 Comments\",
            \"Shares\":\"79 Shares\"
            },

            \"ethiopia\":{
            \"image\":\"@drawable/ethiopia\",
            \"date\":\"July 27 at 21:25\",
            \"text\":\"Received the Prime Minister of Ethiopia, His Excellency Hailemariam Desalegn at State House-Entebbe, this afternoon. We held talks and discussed matters of mutual interest to both Uganda and Ethiopia, like strengthening our Defence ties.\",
            \"likes\":\"1.5K Likes\",
            \"Comments\":\"800 Comments\",
            \"Shares\":\"79 Shares\"
            },

            \"farming\":{
            \"image\":\"@drawable/farming\",
            \"date\":\"July 27 at 21:25\",
            \"text\":\"At Mr Cypriano Okello`s farm at Imakioboro village, Awiepek parish,Aloi, Alebtong District. He has demonstrated how commercial farming does boost household income, engaging in fish farming, fruit growing and apiary, earning about 100m shillings per annum.\",
            \"likes\":\"1.5K Likes\",
            \"Comments\":\"800 Comments\",
            \"Shares\":\"79 Shares\"
            },

            \"russians\":{
            \"image\":\"@drawable/russians\",
            \"date\":\"July 27 at 21:25\",
            \"text\":\"Held a meeting with Mr. Alexander Lebedev, Mr. Evgeny Lebedev and the business delegation from Russia, yesterday at Nakasero State Lodge.\",
            \"likes\":\"1.5K Likes\",
            \"Comments\":\"800 Comments\",
            \"Shares\":\"79 Shares\"
            },

            \"bujumbura\":{
            \"image\":\"@drawable/bujumbura\",
            \"date\":\"July 27 at 21:25\",
            \"text\":\"This evening we concluded the High Level Dialogue on peace in Bujumbura. I want to assure the people of Burundi that the Government and opposition political leaders, Burundi eminent leaders who include former Presidents of the Republic of Burundi, namely Domitien Ndayizaye, Sylvestre Ntibantunganya and Jean Baptist Bagaza, religious leaders, representatives of the Civil Society Organisations and all stakeholders who attended the the High Level Dialogue on peace in Burundi, have agreed to continue the Peace dialogue and negotiate unconditionally and expeditiously in order to reach agreement on issues affecting their country and report back as soon as possible.\",
            \"likes\":\"1.5K Likes\",
            \"Comments\":\"800 Comments\",
            \"Shares\":\"79 Shares\"
            }


        ]

    </string>

    <string name="image_description">Awesome Image</string>
    <string name="date_time">July 27 at 21:25</string>

    <string name="farming">As we wrap up our first tour of Eastern Uganda, I would like to send a special thank you message to all who came to share with me. I am deeply humbled by your commitment to the message of change.</string>
    <string name="bujumbura">I would also like to sympathise with all those peaceful Ugandans that assembled to hear the message and who suffered the effects from teargas and unnecessary police violence. Specifically the people of Soroti and Jinja.</string>
    <string name="ethiopia">I will be heading to Northern Uganda next week and hope to share with you on a number of pertinent issues affecting the region and how we can Go Forward to build a better, stronger, prosperous Uganda.</string>
    <string name="revenue">I would like to thank the entire population of Busoga for the warm welcome I received yesterday. It is humbling to see the solidarity we had despite the heavy police deployment.</string>
    <string name="russians">The consultative meeting did indeed take place at the Nile Village Hotel after numerous efforts by the Uganda Police to sabotage each arrangement that the team put in place.</string>

</resources>
